Tufts Weekly UP056
Tufts Archival Research Center
Tufts Weekly
1895 -- 1968
Tufts Archival Research Center
Office for Campus Life
UP056
4.8 Linear Feet
62 Volumes
19.78 Gigabytes
2079 Digital Object(s)
Arrangement
This collection is organized into one series.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains issue of The Tufts Weekly. It covered college and university news, sports, and events. In its earliest days it also had a literary aspect, but was always primarily concerned with news of the campus written by students. The Weekly contained editorials, announcements, advertising, and calendar items of events. With some exceptions, each volume covers one academic year.
The Tufts Weekly was the student newspaper from 1895 through 1968. It was replaced by the Observer in 1969. Four issues of the Tufts News was published in 1912 by the Class of 1913 as a temporary substitute for The Tufts Weekly, cataloged at end of series 1.
Related Materials
UP055, Tufts Observer, DCA
Biographical / Historical
Responsibility for new student orientation once fell under the purview of the Orientation Committee. Currently, the Office for Campus Life takes a leadership role in the planning and implementation of New Student Orientation.
- Tufts Weekly, 1895 -- 1968; UP056.001; 2.4 Linear Feet; 62 Volumes; 19.78 Gigabytes; 2079 Digital Object(s)
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains issues of The Tufts Weekly. It was the student newspaper from 1895 through 1968. It was replaced by the Observer in 1969.
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged chronologically.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Physical condition. Open for research.
  - Tufts Weekly, 1895 October 08; UP056.001.001.00001 (Box 1)
    Physical condition.
  - Tufts Weekly, 1895 October 15; UP056.001.001.00002 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1895 October 22; UP056.001.001.00003 (Box 1)
    Alpha Kappa Kappa.
  - Tufts Weekly, 1895 October 29; UP056.001.001.00004 (Box 1)
    Alpha Tau Omega.
  - Tufts Weekly, 1895 November 05; UP056.001.001.00005 (Box 1)
    Alpha Kappa Delta.
  - Tufts Weekly, 1895 November 12; UP056.001.001.00006 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1895 November 19; UP056.001.001.00007 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1895 November 26; UP056.001.001.00008 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1895 December 03; UP056.001.001.00009 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1895 December 10; UP056.001.001.00010 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1895 December 17; UP056.001.001.00011 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1896 January 07; UP056.001.001.00012 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1896 January 14; UP056.001.001.00013 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1896 January 21; UP056.001.001.00014 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1896 January 28; UP056.001.001.00015 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1896 February 04; UP056.001.001.00016 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1896 February 11; UP056.001.001.00017 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1896 February 18; UP056.001.001.00018 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1896 February 25; UP056.001.001.00019 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1896 March 10; UP056.001.001.00020 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1896 March 17; UP056.001.001.00021 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1896 March 24; UP056.001.001.00022 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1896 April 07; UP056.001.001.00023 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1896 April 14; UP056.001.001.00024 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1896 April 22; UP056.001.001.00025 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1896 April 28; UP056.001.001.00026 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1896 May 05; UP056.001.001.00027 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1896 May 12; UP056.001.001.00028 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1896 May 19; UP056.001.001.00029 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1896 May 26; UP056.001.001.00030 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1896 June 02; UP056.001.001.00031 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1896 June 09; UP056.001.001.00032 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1896 June 16; UP056.001.001.00033 (Box 1)
    Alumni day
  - Tufts Weekly, 1896 September 29; UP056.001.001.00034; 1 Digital Object(s); 5.78 Megabytes (Box 1)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1896 October 06; UP056.001.001.00035; 1 Digital Object(s); 5.59 Megabytes (Box 1)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1896 October 13; UP056.001.001.00036; 1 Digital Object(s); 5.54 Megabytes (Box 1)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1896 October 20; UP056.001.001.00037; 1 Digital Object(s); 5.64 Megabytes (Box 1)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1896 October 27; UP056.001.001.00038; 1 Digital Object(s); 5.47 Megabytes (Box 1)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1896 November 03; UP056.001.001.00039; 1 Digital Object(s); 5.47 Megabytes (Box 1)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1896 November 10; UP056.001.001.00040; 1 Digital Object(s); 5.42 Megabytes (Box 1)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1896 November 17; UP056.001.001.00041; 1 Digital Object(s); 5.75 Megabytes (Box 1)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1896 November 24; UP056.001.001.00042; 1 Digital Object(s); 5.64 Megabytes (Box 1)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1896 December 01; UP056.001.001.00043; 1 Digital Object(s); 5.70 Megabytes (Box 1)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1896 December 08; UP056.001.001.00044; 1 Digital Object(s); 4.17 Megabytes (Box 1)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1896 December 15; UP056.001.001.00045; 1 Digital Object(s); 4.19 Megabytes (Box 1)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1896 December 22; UP056.001.001.00046; 1 Digital Object(s); 4.11 Megabytes (Box 1)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1897 January 12; UP056.001.001.00047; 1 Digital Object(s); 4.36 Megabytes (Box 1)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1897 January 19; UP056.001.001.00048; 1 Digital Object(s); 3.81 Megabytes (Box 1)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1897 January 26; UP056.001.001.00049; 1 Digital Object(s); 5.27 Megabytes (Box 1)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1897 February 02; UP056.001.001.00050; 1 Digital Object(s); 3.96 Megabytes (Box 1)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1897 February 10; UP056.001.001.00051; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.71 Megabytes (Box 1)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1897 February 17; UP056.001.001.00052; 1 Digital Object(s); 5.28 Megabytes (Box 1)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1897 February 24; UP056.001.001.00053; 1 Digital Object(s); 5.16 Megabytes (Box 1)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1897 March 03; UP056.001.001.00054; 1 Digital Object(s); 5.43 Megabytes (Box 1)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1897 March 10; UP056.001.001.00055; 1 Digital Object(s); 5.35 Megabytes (Box 1)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1897 March 17; UP056.001.001.00056; 1 Digital Object(s); 4.11 Megabytes (Box 1)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1897 March 24; UP056.001.001.00057; 1 Digital Object(s); 4.08 Megabytes (Box 1)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1897 April 07; UP056.001.001.00058; 1 Digital Object(s); 9.58 Megabytes (Box 1)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1897 April 14; UP056.001.001.00059; 1 Digital Object(s); 4.00 Megabytes (Box 1)
    [Alumni 1897]
  - Tufts Weekly, 1897 April 21; UP056.001.001.00060; 1 Digital Object(s); 4.06 Megabytes (Box 1)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1897 April 28; UP056.001.001.00061; 1 Digital Object(s); 5.35 Megabytes (Box 1)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1897 May 05; UP056.001.001.00062; 1 Digital Object(s); 5.37 Megabytes (Box 1)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1897 May 12; UP056.001.001.00063; 1 Digital Object(s); 7.26 Megabytes (Box 1)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1897 May 19; UP056.001.001.00064; 1 Digital Object(s); 5.36 Megabytes (Box 1)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1897 May 26; UP056.001.001.00065; 1 Digital Object(s); 5.49 Megabytes (Box 1)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1897 June 02; UP056.001.001.00066; 1 Digital Object(s); 5.56 Megabytes (Box 1)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1897 June 09; UP056.001.001.00067; 1 Digital Object(s); 7.16 Megabytes (Box 1)
    Alumni association meetings
  - Tufts Weekly, 1897 October 06; UP056.001.001.00068 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1897 October 13; UP056.001.001.00069 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1897 October 20; UP056.001.001.00070 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1897 October 27; UP056.001.001.00071 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1897 November 03; UP056.001.001.00072 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1897 November 10; UP056.001.001.00073 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1897 November 17; UP056.001.001.00074 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1897 December 08; UP056.001.001.00075 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1897 December 15; UP056.001.001.00076 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1897 December 22; UP056.001.001.00077 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1898 January 12; UP056.001.001.00078 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1898 January 19; UP056.001.001.00079 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1898 January 26; UP056.001.001.00080 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1898 February 02; UP056.001.001.00081 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1898 February 09; UP056.001.001.00082 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1898 February 16; UP056.001.001.00083 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1898 February 23; UP056.001.001.00084 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1898 March 02; UP056.001.001.00085 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1898 March 09; UP056.001.001.00086 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1898 March 16; UP056.001.001.00087 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1898 March 23; UP056.001.001.00088 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1898 March 30; UP056.001.001.00089 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1898 April 13; UP056.001.001.00090 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1898 April 20; UP056.001.001.00091 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1898 April 27; UP056.001.001.00092 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1898 May 04; UP056.001.001.00093 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1898 May 11; UP056.001.001.00094 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1898 May 18; UP056.001.001.00095 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1898 May 25; UP056.001.001.00096 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1898 June 01; UP056.001.001.00097 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1898 June 08; UP056.001.001.00098 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1898 October 05; UP056.001.002.00001; 1 Digital Object(s); 7.19 Megabytes (Box 2)
    Open for research.
  - Tufts Weekly, 1898 October 12; UP056.001.002.00002; 1 Digital Object(s); 7.24 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1898 October 19; UP056.001.002.00003; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.67 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1898 October 26; UP056.001.002.00004; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.83 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1898 November 02; UP056.001.002.00005; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.58 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1898 November 09; UP056.001.002.00006; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.95 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1898 November 16; UP056.001.002.00007; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.56 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1898 November 23; UP056.001.002.00008; 1 Digital Object(s); 7.87 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1898 December 07; UP056.001.002.00009; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.53 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1898 December 14; UP056.001.002.00010; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.56 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1898 December 21; UP056.001.002.00011; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.29 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1899 January 11; UP056.001.002.00012; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.36 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1899 January 18; UP056.001.002.00013; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.68 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1899 January 25; UP056.001.002.00014; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.76 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1899 February 01; UP056.001.002.00015; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.49 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1899 February 08; UP056.001.002.00016; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.72 Megabytes (Box 2)
    Daniel Gustavius Abbott (1886). Death of, January 30, 1899. (page 2) [Alpha Tau Omega] Purchased Joy House, corner of Curtis Avenue and Curtis St.
  - Tufts Weekly, 1899 February 15; UP056.001.002.00017; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.39 Megabytes (Box 2)
    [Alpha Tau Omega] Report that ATO bought Joy House false.
  - Tufts Weekly, 1899 February 22; UP056.001.002.00018; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.45 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1899 March 01; UP056.001.002.00019; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.41 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1899 March 08; UP056.001.002.00020; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.24 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1899 March 15; UP056.001.002.00021; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.80 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1899 March 22; UP056.001.002.00022; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.25 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1899 March 29; UP056.001.002.00023; 1 Digital Object(s); 5.94 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1899 April 12; UP056.001.002.00024; 1 Digital Object(s); 5.95 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1899 April 19; UP056.001.002.00025; 1 Digital Object(s); 5.79 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1899 April 26; UP056.001.002.00026; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.06 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1899 May 03; UP056.001.002.00027; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.02 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1899 May 10; UP056.001.002.00028; 1 Digital Object(s); 5.99 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1899 May 17; UP056.001.002.00029; 1 Digital Object(s); 5.67 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1899 May 24; UP056.001.002.00030; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.21 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1899 May 31; UP056.001.002.00031; 1 Digital Object(s); 5.67 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1899 June 07; UP056.001.002.00032; 1 Digital Object(s); 5.93 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1899 June 14; UP056.001.002.00033; 1 Digital Object(s); 5.92 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1899 October 04; UP056.001.002.00034; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.19 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1899 October 11; UP056.001.002.00035; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.25 Megabytes (Box 2)
    All Around Club.
  - Tufts Weekly, 1899 October 18; UP056.001.002.00036; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.02 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1899 October 25; UP056.001.002.00037; 1 Digital Object(s); 7.25 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1899 November 01; UP056.001.002.00038; 1 Digital Object(s); 7.27 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1899 November 08; UP056.001.002.00039; 1 Digital Object(s); 7.47 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1899 November 15; UP056.001.002.00040; 1 Digital Object(s); 7.23 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1899 November 22; UP056.001.002.00041; 1 Digital Object(s); 7.29 Megabytes (Box 2)
    All Around Club. Alpha Tau Omega.
  - Tufts Weekly, 1899 December 06; UP056.001.002.00042; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.95 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1899 December 15; UP056.001.002.00043; 1 Digital Object(s); 7.14 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1900 January 10; UP056.001.002.00044; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.53 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1900 January 17; UP056.001.002.00045; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.42 Megabytes (Box 2)
    [Alpha Kappa Kappa] Fraternity buys house on West Newton Street.
  - Tufts Weekly, 1900 January 24; UP056.001.002.00046; 1 Digital Object(s); 7.40 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1900 January 31; UP056.001.002.00047; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.56 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1900 February 07; UP056.001.002.00048; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.46 Megabytes (Box 2)
    [Alumni] System of registration arranged by faculty committee
  - Tufts Weekly, 1900 February 14; UP056.001.002.00049; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.95 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1900 February 21; UP056.001.002.00050; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.87 Megabytes (Box 2)
    Alpha Kappa Delta. Alpha Tau Omega.
  - Tufts Weekly, 1900 March 07; UP056.001.002.00051; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.73 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1900 March 14; UP056.001.002.00052; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.10 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1900 March 21; UP056.001.002.00053; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.22 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1900 March 28; UP056.001.002.00054; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.77 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1900 April 11; UP056.001.002.00055; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.60 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1900 April 18; UP056.001.002.00056; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.35 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1900 May 01; UP056.001.002.00057; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.50 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1900 May 09; UP056.001.002.00058; 1 Digital Object(s); 5.74 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1900 May 16; UP056.001.002.00059; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.04 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1900 May 23; UP056.001.002.00060; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.07 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1900 June 06; UP056.001.002.00061; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.39 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1900 June 20; UP056.001.002.00062; 1 Digital Object(s); 10.96 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1900 October 03; UP056.001.002.00063; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.28 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1900 October 10; UP056.001.002.00064; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.22 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1900 October 17; UP056.001.002.00065; 1 Digital Object(s); 7.02 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1900 October 24; UP056.001.002.00066; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.91 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1900 October 31; UP056.001.002.00067; 1 Digital Object(s); 7.05 Megabytes (Box 2)
    All Around Club. Alpha Kappa Delta.
  - Tufts Weekly, 1900 November 07; UP056.001.002.00068; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.82 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1900 November 14; UP056.001.002.00069; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.63 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1900 November 21; UP056.001.002.00070; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.64 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1900 December 05; UP056.001.002.00071; 1 Digital Object(s); 5.78 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1900 December 12; UP056.001.002.00072; 1 Digital Object(s); 5.75 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1901 January 09; UP056.001.002.00073; 1 Digital Object(s); 5.70 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1901 January 16; UP056.001.002.00074; 1 Digital Object(s); 5.52 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1901 January 23; UP056.001.002.00075; 1 Digital Object(s); 5.62 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1901 January 30; UP056.001.002.00076; 1 Digital Object(s); 5.33 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1901 February 06; UP056.001.002.00077; 1 Digital Object(s); 5.62 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1901 February 13; UP056.001.002.00078; 1 Digital Object(s); 5.79 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1901 February 27; UP056.001.002.00079; 1 Digital Object(s); 5.97 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1901 March 06; UP056.001.002.00080; 1 Digital Object(s); 5.81 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1901 March 13; UP056.001.002.00081; 1 Digital Object(s); 5.95 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1901 March 20; UP056.001.002.00082; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.03 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1901 March 27; UP056.001.002.00083; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.36 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1901 April 10; UP056.001.002.00084; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.50 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1901 April 17; UP056.001.002.00085; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.17 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1901 April 24; UP056.001.002.00086; 1 Digital Object(s); 5.90 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1901 May 01; UP056.001.002.00087; 1 Digital Object(s); 5.30 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1901 May 08; UP056.001.002.00088; 1 Digital Object(s); 5.77 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1901 May 15; UP056.001.002.00089; 1 Digital Object(s); 7.28 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1901 May 22; UP056.001.002.00090; 1 Digital Object(s); 7.27 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1901 May 29; UP056.001.002.00091; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.92 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1901 June 05; UP056.001.002.00092; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.94 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1901 June 12; UP056.001.002.00093; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.55 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1901 June 19; UP056.001.002.00094; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.89 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1901 September 26; UP056.001.003.00001; 1 Digital Object(s); 5.34 Megabytes (Box 3)
    All Around Club. [Allen House] Rooming accomodations for women students.
  - Tufts Weekly, 1901 October 03; UP056.001.003.00002; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.21 Megabytes (Box 3)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1901 October 10; UP056.001.003.00003; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.69 Megabytes (Box 3)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1901 October 17; UP056.001.003.00004; 1 Digital Object(s); 7.20 Megabytes (Box 3)
    Additional user copy in the Reading Room.
  - Tufts Weekly, 1901 October 24; UP056.001.003.00005; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.92 Megabytes (Box 3)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1901 October 31; UP056.001.003.00006; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.99 Megabytes (Box 3)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1901 November 07; UP056.001.003.00007; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.65 Megabytes (Box 3)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1901 November 14; UP056.001.003.00008; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.76 Megabytes (Box 3)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1901 November 21; UP056.001.003.00009; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.55 Megabytes (Box 3)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1901 December 05; UP056.001.003.00010; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.25 Megabytes (Box 3)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1901 December 12; UP056.001.003.00011; 1 Digital Object(s); 5.77 Megabytes (Box 3)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1901 December 17; UP056.001.003.00012; 1 Digital Object(s); 5.94 Megabytes (Box 3)
    [Admissions, 1901] New Entrance Requirements.
  - Tufts Weekly, 1902 January 09; UP056.001.003.00013; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.07 Megabytes (Box 3)
    All Around Club. Alpha Tau Omega; Alumni dance, pg 1
  - Tufts Weekly, 1902 January 16; UP056.001.003.00014; 1 Digital Object(s); 5.81 Megabytes (Box 3)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1902 January 23; UP056.001.003.00015; 1 Digital Object(s); 5.63 Megabytes (Box 3)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1902 January 30; UP056.001.003.00016; 1 Digital Object(s); 5.71 Megabytes (Box 3)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1902 February 06; UP056.001.003.00017; 1 Digital Object(s); 5.92 Megabytes (Box 3)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1902 February 13; UP056.001.003.00018; 1 Digital Object(s); 5.94 Megabytes (Box 3)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1902 February 20; UP056.001.003.00019; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.45 Megabytes (Box 3)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1902 February 27; UP056.001.003.00020; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.39 Megabytes (Box 3)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1902 March 06; UP056.001.003.00021; 1 Digital Object(s); 5.76 Megabytes (Box 3)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1902 March 13; UP056.001.003.00022; 1 Digital Object(s); 5.23 Megabytes (Box 3)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1902 March 20; UP056.001.003.00023; 1 Digital Object(s); 5.54 Megabytes (Box 3)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1902 March 27; UP056.001.003.00024; 1 Digital Object(s); 5.73 Megabytes (Box 3)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1902 April 03; UP056.001.003.00025; 1 Digital Object(s); 5.34 Megabytes (Box 3)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1902 April 17; UP056.001.003.00026; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.35 Megabytes (Box 3)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1902 April 24; UP056.001.003.00027; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.72 Megabytes (Box 3)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1902 May 01; UP056.001.003.00028; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.09 Megabytes (Box 3)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1902 May 08; UP056.001.003.00029; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.23 Megabytes (Box 3)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1902 May 15; UP056.001.003.00030; 1 Digital Object(s); 7.03 Megabytes (Box 3)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1902 May 22; UP056.001.003.00031; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.26 Megabytes (Box 3)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1902 May 29; UP056.001.003.00032; 1 Digital Object(s); 5.34 Megabytes (Box 3)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1902 June 04; UP056.001.003.00033; 1 Digital Object(s); 5.29 Megabytes (Box 3)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1902 June 11; UP056.001.003.00034; 1 Digital Object(s); 5.12 Megabytes (Box 3)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1902 June 19; UP056.001.003.00035; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.88 Megabytes (Box 3)
    Commencement Supplement
  - Tufts Weekly, 1902 September 24; UP056.001.003.00036; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.33 Megabytes (Box 3)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1902 October 01; UP056.001.003.00037; 1 Digital Object(s); 5.66 Megabytes (Box 3)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1902 October 08; UP056.001.003.00038; 1 Digital Object(s); 5.67 Megabytes (Box 3)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1902 October 16; UP056.001.003.00039; 1 Digital Object(s); 5.74 Megabytes (Box 3)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1902 October 23; UP056.001.003.00040; 1 Digital Object(s); 5.80 Megabytes (Box 3)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1902 October 30; UP056.001.003.00041; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.08 Megabytes (Box 3)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1902 November 06; UP056.001.003.00042; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.13 Megabytes (Box 3)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1902 November 13; UP056.001.003.00043; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.01 Megabytes (Box 3)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1902 November 20; UP056.001.003.00044; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.00 Megabytes (Box 3)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1902 December 04; UP056.001.003.00045; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.05 Megabytes (Box 3)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1902 December 11; UP056.001.003.00046; 1 Digital Object(s); 5.63 Megabytes (Box 3)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1902 December 18; UP056.001.003.00047; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.08 Megabytes (Box 3)
  - Tufts Weekly, 1903 January 08; UP056.001.003.00048; 1 Digital Object(s); 5.97 Megabytes (Box 3)